hotsouthindiansex.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy And Cookie Policy - Hotsouthindiansex.com

Effective May 21, 2018

## Introduction

Your access and use of this site signifies that you have read, understood, and agreed to all terms within this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms, do not continue to use this website.

We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of Hotsouthindiansex.com. This Privacy Policy may be updated on occasion. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. Should you have any questions about this policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer at the email address listed below.

This site expressly and strictly limits its viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over, or having attained the age of majority in their country. All persons who do not meet this criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

The security of your Data is very important to Hotsouthindiansex.com and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our site, application, services, features and content, to administer your account and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the site.

This Privacy Policy applies to the information we collect on the website Hotsouthindiansex.com, both mobile and desktop versions. It also applies for any correspondance between this site, the administrators, and you. For example, this may include communication by email or text.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information collected by any third-party (such as advertisers on the website) that may link to or be accessible from or on Hotsouthindiansex.com. Clicking on advertisements which take a user from Hotsouthindiansex.com to another website may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We do not control these third-party websites and are not responsible for their privacy statements.

## Personal Information

Personal data, or personal information, pertains to any information about an individual from which that person can be identified by. It does not include data that has been rendered anonymous.

Non-registered users are those that visit the site without logging in or creating a user account. These users may visit the site and watch videos or view photos.

For non-registered users, we may collect, use, store and transfer certain personal information about you, including:

  * Technical Data such as: 
    * the visitor's IP address, which we store in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content.
    * browser type and version
    * time zone setting and location
    * operating system and platform
    * information on device used to access the website
    * User-submitted Data which includes data collected following a specific action the user has taken, such as filling out information for a contest or a survey
    * Usage Data which includes aggregated information about how you use Hotsouthindiansex.com

Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

## Information Collected Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies

As you interact with Hotsouthindiansex.com, we use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device information, search terms, and cookie information.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

Cookies (or browser cookies). Cookies are small text files that are stored in your web browser or downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognizes that cookie, and allow a website to recognize a user’s device.

We currently use the following types of cookies:

Cookies that are strictly necessary: These are cookies that are required for the operation of our Website. These include, for example, cookies that enable a user to log in to our Website and to check if a user is allowed access to a particular service or content.

Analytical cookies: These cookies allow us to recognize and count the number of users and to see how users use and explore our Website. These cookies help us to improve our Website, for example by ensuring that all users are able to find what they are looking for easily.

Functionality cookies: These cookies are not essential, but help us to personalize and enhance your online experience on our Website. This type of cookies allows us to recognize you when you return to our Website and to remember, for example, your choice of language.

Targeting cookies: These cookies record the visit of a user on our Website, the pages a user has visited and the links a user has followed in order to enable us to make our Website more relevant to the users' interests.

We do not require that you accept cookies and you may withdraw your consent to our use of cookies at any time by adjusting your browser’s privacy settings. However, if you decline to accept cookies, some functionality on our Website may be disabled and you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. Cookies can be either session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires automatically when you close your browser. A persistent cookie will remain until it expires or you delete your cookies. Expiration dates are set in the cookies themselves; some may expire after a few minutes while others may expire after multiple years.

Pixel Tags. Pages of our Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as pixel tags (also known as clear gifs, pixel tags, single-pixel gifs, web beacons, and web bugs) that are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users or to access cookies.

Analytics. We use third party analytics and advertising tools and technologies, in particular Google Analytics provided by Google, Inc., USA (“Google”). These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, media access control address (MAC Address), mobile unique device identifiers, and other similar information via the use of cookies. The information generated by Google Analytics about your use of the Website (including your IP address) may be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers.

## Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our Website. Unless expressly stated otherwise, our website does not provide any Personal Information to these third parties, however they may collect information, including Personal Information, such as internet protocol (IP) address, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this Website. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

## HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

The personally identifiable information you submit to Hotsouthindiansex.com is used to provide the user with special, personalized site features.

Your chosen username (not your email address) is displayed to other Users alongside the content you upload, including pictures & videos, comments, likes, etc.

Any pictures or videos that you submit to Hotsouthindiansex.com may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

We may use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages.

We may use your email address for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes).

Opt-in communication — Subscriber expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his/her email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may be used to send him/her offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications. More specifically, some offers may be presented to the subscriber via email campaigns or other means of communications with the option to express the subscriber's preference by either clicking or entering "accept" (alternatively "yes") or "decline" (alternatively "no"). By selecting or clicking the "accept" or "yes", the subscriber indicates that the subscriber "OPTS-IN" to that offer and thereby agrees and assents that the subscriber's personal information, including its email address and data may be used for that matter."

Opt-out communication — Subscriber expressly and specifically acknowledges and agrees that his/her email address or other means of communicating with subscriber may not be used to send him/her offers, information or any other commercially oriented emails or other means of communications.

We analyze aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the Hotsouthindiansex.com user-experience. Examples of this may include collecting your Usage Data to determine what percentage of all users visited a certain page.

## DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

If required to do so, Hotsouthindiansex.com may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of Hotsouthindiansex.com or our subscribers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations including the police and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms of Service. It is Hotsouthindiansex.com's policy, whenever possible and legally permissible, to promptly notify you upon an obligation to supply data to any third party.

Should you deliberately upload any illegal material, Hotsouthindiansex.com shall forward all available information to all relevant authorities and do so without notice.

We do not share your personally identifiable information, such as email address, with other third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent, or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

We may disclose your personal information to authorized service providers that perform services on our behalf. These services may include but are not limited to 3rd party email management software, fulfillment of orders, providing customer service, performing business or sales analysis, and aggregated data analysis software.

We may also disclose your information in the case where there is a legal successor. In the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or any other type of sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, the information in our possession may be transferred to the successor.

We may disclose aggregated information about our users which does not identify any individual, without any restriction.

Transfers of Your Personal Information to Other Countries

Whenever in the course of sharing information we transfer Personal Information to countries outside of the European Economic Area and other regions with comprehensive data protection laws, we will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this privacy policy and as permitted by the applicable laws on data protection.

By using the Website you consent to the transfer of information that we collect about you, including personal information, to any country in which we or our service providers are located.

## LINKS TO OTHER SITES

Our site contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by "clicking on" a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

## SECURITY

We have given you, or you have chosen, a password, which enables you to access certain parts of our Site. You are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Hotsouthindiansex.com uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Hotsouthindiansex.com, and you do so at your own risk.

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to us. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, login information, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission's website.

## YOUR RIGHTS

All registered users may review, update, correct or delete the personal information in their account by contacting us or by editing your profile via the site. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

In accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation law in the EU effective May 25, 2018, users of this site may request a copy of their personal data as well as request that their personal data be deleted. Official identification shall be required to confirm your identity. In order to make such a request, contact our Data Protection Officer using the address below.

## CONTACTING US

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer at:

webmaster(at)Hotsouthindiansex.com
